dustygroove.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy -- Dusty Groove is Chicago's Online Record Store

* * *

## Your Privacy

We respect your privacy and do not tolerate spam. We will not rent or sell your name, address, email address, credit card information or any other personal information to anyone, unless legally required to do so. 

**We do not share browsing or buying patterns with any third parties or other companies.**

We do not participate in advertising networks and do not track searches or product browsing across multiple websites. We may obtain information about customers from other sources to verify name, address and/or contact information. We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use our site. We receive this information in aggregate and not on an individual basis, making use of "IP masking". To read more about how Google uses personal information visit [privacy.google.com](https://privacy.google.com/). 

We do not use any advertising on the Dusty Groove website. We do use Google Adwords on sites other than our own. We track inbound paid advertising referrals to improve our advertising performance. 

We provide a Share button on some of our web pages. Clicking the share button will display buttons for Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest which may provide a personalized social media experience on those sites. 

We display your recently viewed items on certain pages for ease of navigation. The website formulates the "Suggested Titles" page by looking at a customer's order history, cart, watch list, and viewing history to create a list of titles that appear to have interested the customer in the past. Those titles are supplied to the recommendation lookup scheme to create a personalized list of suggested titles. The information that is used to create this list is available on the customer's account page and was provided by the customer. No personalized data is used that cannot be found on the customer's account page. 

When an account is created on the Dusty Groove website we send notifications regarding account activity, orders, and occasional special announcements. Customers may subscribe to or opt out of receiving newsletters and special announcements at any time. 

You have the right to access personal information we hold about your and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If your would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the information below. 

If you have any additional questions about your information or our policies, please contact us at [privacy@dustygroove.com](mailto:privacy@dustygroove.com). 

## Security

Dusty Groove uses the latest encryption technology to protect credit card and other personal information. All pages are served and all transactions, such as account creating and order placement, are conducted using secure HTTP connections (TLS 1.2, the successor to SSL). This protocol encrypts all of the information send to us, including credit card numbers, names, addresses and phone numbers, so that this information cannot be hacked or intercepted by anyone on the internet. 

**Browsers using previous SSL and TLS protocols (SSL 2, SSL 3, TLS 1.0, TLS 1.1) will not connect to the website after July 2018** because banks and financial institutions (the Payment Card Industry) require that merchants use TLS 1.2 to accept credit cards online as of this date. Customers using a browser that does not support TLS 1.2 are recommend to upgrade their browser so they can continue to visit the Dusty Groove website. This is strictly for customer security and PCI compliance. 

You can find out how well your client handles secure connections at [https://www.howsmyssl.com](https://www.howsmyssl.com/). 

[Private browsing](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Private_browsing), or "incognito mode", is supported by Dusty Groove and encouraged where appropriate. 

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser. We do not store any personal information in cookies, but we use them to identify customer accounts, manage orders, and maintain website preferences while shopping. We do not track user activity across other websites and do not use cookies to share profile information with third-party marketers. We will never give or sell personal information to anyone. 

## Changes to Our Policy

Our Policy is intended to provide you with the safest and most secure shopping experience possible. 

Since technologies change, we reserve the right to modify, add, or remove portions of our Privacy Policy. Please periodically review this page for changes. This policy is effective from June 2018.
